$SD_CONCAT_{}DAYS_{}HOURS	{} days, {} hours.
$SD_CONCAT_EXACTLY{}YARDS	Exactly {} yards.
$SD_CONCAT_BETWEEN{}AND{}YARDS	Between {} and {} yards.
$SD_CONCAT_EXACTLY{}METERS	Exactly {} meters.
$SD_CONCAT_BETWEEN{}AND{}METERS	Between {} and {} meters.
$SD_CONCAT{}VERSION	Version: {}
$SD_CONCAT{}STATUS	Status: {}
$SD_CONCAT_KEYMAP{}_CONFLICT{}_CONTUNUE	This key is already mapped to ' {} ' ( {} ). Are you sure you want to continue?
$SD_CONCAT_KEYMAP{}_CONTUNUE	This key is already mapped to ' {} '. Are you sure you want to continue?
$SD_HEALTH	{1}x health
$SD_PERCENT_HEALTH	{0}% health
$SD_GOLD	{0} gold
$SD_UNITS	{0} units
$SD_SECONDS	{0} seconds
$SD_DAYS	{3} days
$SD_PERCENT	{0}%
$SD_HELP	HELP
$SD_OK	OK
$SD_NO	NO
$SD_YES	YES
$SD_RUNNING	Running
$SD_STOPPED	Stopped
$SD_STOPPING	Stopping
$SD_STARTING	Starting
$SD_QUEST_STATUS	Quest Status
$SD_STATE	state
$SD_STAGE	stage
$SD_PAGE_CONFIG	Configuration
$SD_PAGE_STATUS	Status
$SD_PAGE_CONTROL	Controls
$SD_PAGE_ADDONS	Addons & Mods
$SD_PAGE_HELP	Help
$SD_GENDER_NO	No
$SD_GENDER_SAME	Same Only
$SD_GENDER_OPPOSITE	Opposite Only
$SD_MOD_STATE_RUNNING	Enslavement Quests Running
$SD_MOD_STATE_READY_TO_INSTALL	Install Sanguine's Debauchery
$SD_MOD_STATE_READY_TO_BEGIN	Begin Sanguine's Debauchery
$SD_MOD_STATE_PREPARE_FOR_UNINSTALL	Prepare for Uninstall
$SD_MOD_STATE_UNINSTALLED	Mod is in uninstalled state
$SD_MOD_STATE_LOCKED	LOCKED
$SD_MOD_STATE_INSTALL	INSTALL
$SD_MOD_STATE_BEGIN	BEGIN
$SD_MOD_STATE_UNINSTALL	UNINSTALL
$SD_MOD_STATE_RE_INSTALL	RE-INSTALL
$SD_HEADER_P0_COMBAT	Enslavement via Combat
$SD_OPTION_P0_BUFFER	Negative Health Buffer
$SD_OPTION_P0_WEAKENED_AT	Weakened State
$SD_OPTION_P0_ESSENTIAL_WHILE_WEAKENED	Essential While Weakened
$SD_HEADER_P0_ITEMS	Items
$SD_OPTION_P0_LIMITED_REMOVAL	Limited Removal
$SD_HEADER_P0_ORIENTATION	Sexual Orientation
$SD_OPTION_P0_GENDER_RESTRICTION	Gender restriction
$SD_HEADER_P0_NOTIFICATION	Notification
$SD_OPTION_P0_SHOW_DEMERIT_CHANGES	Demerit Changes
$SD_HEADER_P0_NPC_REACTION	NPC Reaction
$SD_OPTION_P0_ENABLE_TRAIN_RUN	Enable train run
$SD_HEADER_P0_BODY	Body
$SD_OPTION_P0_USING_CBBE	Female: Using CBBE
$SD_OPTION_P0_USE_CUSTOM_CLOTHING	Custom Slave Clothing
$SD_OPTION_P0_USE_MALE_ERRECT_BODYSUIT	Male: Using FavoredSoul flaccid version
$SD_HEADER_P0_ESCAPE	Escape
$SD_SLIDER_P0_BYOUT_AMOUNT	Buyout
$SD_SLIDER_P0_ESCAPE_RADIUS	Escape Radius
$SD_SLIDER_P0_ESCAPE_TIMER	Escape Timer
$SD_SLIDER_P0_DAYS_TO_START_TASKS	Start Tasks
$SD_OPTION_P0_HARDCORE	Hardcore Mode
$SD_HEADER_P0_EFFECTS	Effects
$SD_SLIDER_P0_BLINDNESS_LEVEL	Blindfold: Level of darkness.
$SD_HEADER_P1_PRIMARY_QUESTS	Primary Quest Status
$SD_HEADER_P1_SECONDARY_QUESTS	Secondary Quest Status
$SD_TOGGLE_P1_IS_PLAYER_ENSLAVED	Is the player enslaved?
$SD_TOGGLE_P1_IS_ARTIFACT_ENABLED	Sanguine's Daedric Artifact Enabled
$SD_HEADER_P1_ENABLE_DISABLE	Enable / Disable
$SD_UPDATING_QUEST_MSG_LINE_1	Updating quests require that you exit all menus.
$SD_UPDATING_QUEST_MSG_LINE_2	If uninstalling, wait unitl you get a message
$SD_UPDATING_QUEST_MSG_LINE_3	indicating that it's okay to exit the game.
$SD_HEADER_P2_KEYS	Keys
$SD_KEYMAP_P2_POSITION_RESET	Position Reset
$SD_KEYMAP_P2_UNSTICK	Unstick
$SD_KEYMAP_P2_MOVE_UP	Cycle from crawl to stand
$SD_KEYMAP_P2_MOVE_CLOSER	Move Closer
$SD_KEYMAP_P2_MOVE_AWAY	Move Away
$SD_KEYMAP_P2_MOVE_DOWN	Cycle from stand to crawl
$SD_KEYMAP_P2_SURRENDER	Surrender/Submit
$SD_HEADER_P2_KEY_FUNCTIONS	Key Functions
$SD_OPTION_P2_POSITION_RESET_EXPLAIN	Use SexLab to Adjust
$SD_OPTION_P2_UNSTICK_EXPLAIN	Unstick: Move the player to the master/mistress
$SD_OPTION_P2_UNSTICK_EXPLAIN_SHIFT	   Shift + Unstick: End the current scene.
$SD_OPTION_P2_UNSTICK_EXPLAIN_ALT	   Alt + Unstick: Fix target actor animation
$SD_OPTION_P2_MOVE_UP_EXPLAIN	Use SexLab to Adjust
$SD_OPTION_P2_MOVE_CLOSER_EXPLAIN	Use SexLab to Adjust
$SD_OPTION_P2_MOVE_AWAY_EXPLAIN	Use SexLab to Adjust
$SD_OPTION_P2_MOVE_DOWN_EXPLAIN	Use SexLab to Adjust
$SD_OPTION_P2_MOVE_DOWN_EXPLAIN_SHIFT	   Use SexLab to Adjust
$SD_OPTION_P2_SURRENDER_EXPLAIN	Surrender (combat): Surrender to your target
$SD_HEADER_P3_ADDONS	Addons
$SD_OPTION_P3_UPDATING_MUST_EXIT	Updating quests require that you exit all menus.
$SD_HEADER_P3_MODS	Mods
$SD_HEADER_P4_HOWTO	How to...
$SD_TEXT_P4_START_HELP	Start this Mod.
$SD_TEXT_P4_STOP_HELP	Stop this Mod.
$SD_TEXT_P4_GET_ENSLAVED_HELP	Get enslaved.
$SD_TEXT_P4_ESCAPE_HELP	Escape.
$SD_HEADER_P4_QUESTS	Quests
$SD_TEXT_P4_THUGS_HELP	The Thug's never come after me.
$SD_TEXT_P4_SPRIGGAN_ARMOR_HELP	Wearing the Spriggan Armor, now what?
$SD_TEXT_P4_ENSLAVEMENT_COMPLETED_HELP	I'm free but the quest hasn't completed.
$SD_HEADER_P4_OTHER	Other
$SD_TEXT_P4_ARMOR_N_RACES_HELP	Armor & Custom Races
$SD_HEADER_P4_VERIFIED_CONFLICTS	Verified Conflicting Mods
$_SDOID_config_T1	Exit all menus to allow quests to update their status.\nHEY!! DOWN HERE! If you die during the uninstall use TIM in console before and after your next attempt.
$_SDOID_config_T2	Gender restrictions in addition to faction restrictions for enslavement.
$_SDOID_config_B1	During enslavement quest startup the player is made essential. Essential is removed once the quest has fully started.\nDisable this option if you are running a mod that makes the player essential.
$_SDOID_config_B2	This choice must be made before you begin. When enabled, Sanguine's Daedric Artifact (labia rings for female, anal egg for male) is bound to the player and NPCs will experience uncontrollable lust for the player.
$_SDOID_config_B3	When the player is enslaved all non quest player inventory items are transferd to the player's master. If you have mods installed that use special items in the player inventory then the limited option filters objects out that cannot be sold or disenchanted.
$_SDOID_config_B4	UNBP is used by default. Enabling this will use CBBE versions of models when available.\nYou must make this choice before the item is in use.
$_SDOID_config_B5	If you are using FavoredSoul flaccid male model checking this option will swap the male a FavoredSoul erect male model bodysuit.\nYou must install the textures in SD-FavoredSoulMeshes-FlaccidPatch.7z to not get a glowing penis.
$_SDOID_config_B6	You will see a notification whenever you gain ot loose demerits with this option enabled.
$_SDOID_config_B7	Allows for custom slave clothing to be used rather than the default rags. You need to place your custom meshes in 'meshes\\_SD_\\custom\\slave_rags\\'. If this does not look familiar to you or if you don't know what I'm talking about, don't enable this.
$_SDOID_config_B7_MSG	You are not done yet. If you haven't done so already you'll need to open the Creation Kit and update the Armors _SDA_slave_rags_cbbe and/or _SDA_slave_rags_unpb and update the associated armor Add-ons _SDAA_slave_rags_cbbe and/or _SDAA_slave_rags_unpb.\n\nYou should also save.
$_SDOID_config_B8	Enables the NPC queue on the player after dancing. The quest 'Gold for the Wicked' must be running.
$_SDOID_config_B9	Bindings and the like are not auto removed when the player escapes. They must have the master's key or get help from someone.
$_SDOID_config_S1	Sets the limit of the negative health buffer. Go below this and the player is allowed to die.
$_SDOID_config_S2	Percentage of the players base health that the player's current health must be below before enslavement checks are made.
$_SDOID_config_S3	The total gold and item value that the player must give to their master to buy their freedom.
$_SDOID_config_S4	The distance the player must put between their master and themselves to escape.\n
$_SDOID_config_S5	The duration in seconds that the player must spend outside the Escape Radius to escape.
$_SDOID_config_S6	Number of game days that must pass before the player is allowed to work towards their freedom. The current value is: 
$_SDOID_config_S7	Increasing this value will reduce visibility when the player is wearing a blindfold.
$_SDOID_help_T1_1	The first step is to open the Status page, make your selection of what features you want to enable/disable ( you may have to exit MCM a few times ). \n\nIf you selected Immersive Starts, the main quest will start automatically after you visit a location where Sanguine may be lurking (inns, some temples and other surprise locations) or after 'A Night to Remember', whichever comes first.
$_SDOID_help_T2_1	To stop the mod you can use the 'UNINSTALL' option. Clicking that will start the uninstall process.\n\nDO NOT EXIT THE GAME AT THIS POINT. Wait until you get the 'Sanguine's Debauchery is ready to uninstall.' message.
$_SDOID_help_T3_1	Lose in combat. If Death Alternative is installed and SD quests are registered from DA menu, there isn't a quest to start. Rather than being killed, enslavement is triggered when the player is beaten in combat by specified factions. Without Death Alternative, you will need to manually submit using the Surrender Key (by default, '\')
$_SDOID_help_T4_1	Steal the key, kill your master, sucessfully run away, or buy your way out by preforming tasks for your master. You can adjust these on the Configuration page to make it as tough or as easy as you like.
$_SDOID_help_T5_1	The thug quest ( WIAddItem03 ) is the 3rd in the series of four related quests. They must be preformed and completed in sequence before they are cycled through again. See the Troubleshooting section from the Mod post for more info.
$_SDOID_help_T6_1	After the player becomes the host for the spriggan the next stage of the quest is triggered by a few specific comments made by NPCs. You'll get a quest update when it happens. If you have a mod the like 'Reduced Distance NPC Greetings' (Steam) then NPCs will not make comments about the player's unusual appearance and the quest will not proceed.
$_SDOID_help_T7_1	For the Flowering Spriggan Quest or if you escape through a non-hostile method for the Enslavement Quest the quest will not end right away. You've got one game hour to get away before the quest finishes and removes you from any factions you've been added to.
$_SDOID_help_T8_1	This is dependent on the creator of custom race and how they've decided to handle armor. Also if you see hand, feet, mask but no body while wearing the Spriggan armor it's the commom 100% body weight armor bug. You can fix it in console with the following command: 'player.setnpcweight 99'
$SD_STATUS_INSTALLING	Sanguine's Debauchery is installing
$SD_STATUS_INSTALLED	Sanguine's Debauchery has been installed
$SD_STATUS_STARTING	Sanguine's Debauchery is starting
$SD_STATUS_STARTED	Sanguine's Debauchery has been started
$SD_STATUS_STOPPING	Sanguine's Debauchery is stopping
$SD_STATUS_STOPPED	Sanguine's Debauchery has been stopped
$SD_STATUS_RESETTING	Sanguine's Debauchery is resetting
$SD_STATUS_RESET	Sanguine's Debauchery has been reset
$SD_STATUS_UPDATING	Sanguine's Debauchery is updating
$SD_STATUS_UPDATED	Sanguine's Debauchery has been updated
$SD_STATUS_UNINSTALL_1	Sanguine's Debauchery preparing to uninstall.
$SD_STATUS_UNINSTALL_2	You will receive notification when ready.
$SD_STATUS_UNINSTALL_3	Expiring game-time triggered scripts. Or use game wait for 2 hrs.
$SD_STATUS_UNINSTALL_4	Sanguine's Debauchery is ready to uninstall.
$SD_MESSAGE_WAIT_5_SEC	Wait at least 5 seconds between attempts.
$SD_MESSAGE_GAGGED	You cannot eat or drink when gagged.
$SD_MESSAGE_MASTER_AWARE	Checking Master's reaction / awareness
$SD_MESSAGE_CAUGHT	You have been caught!
$SD_MESSAGE_ESCAPE_NOW	Now is your chance to escape!
$SD_MESSAGE_ESCAPE_GONE	Your chance to escape is gone.
$SD_MESSAGE_STAY_CLOSE_TO_MASTER	You should stay close to you master
$SD_MESSAGE_STAY_AWAY_FROM_WEAPONS	You should stay away from weapons and the like when close to your master.
$SD_MESSAGE_MASTER_IS_DEAD_LUCK	Your new Master is dead. Lucky you.
$SD_MESSAGE_MASTER_SUSPICIOUS	Your master grows suspicious.
$SD_MESSAGE_TRYING_TO_SURRENDER	Trying to surrender
$SD_MESSAGE_MAKE_LOCKPICK	You manage to break apart the weapon.
$SD_MESSAGE_FAIL_LOCKPICK	You can't use this as a lockpick. It's been ruined.



$Male	Male
$Female	Female
$Use gender restriction	Use gender restriction

$Chance of enslavement	Chance of enslavement
$Chance of spriggan infection	Chance of spriggan infection
$Percent health to submit	Percent health to submit


$Slave Options	Slave Options
$Enable Armbinder Kneeling	Enable Armbinder Kneeling
$Enable Beast Enslavement	Enable Beast Enslavement
$Enable Cage scenes	Enable Cage scenes
$Enable Coveted effect	Enable Coveted effect
$Min slavery level	Min slavery level
$Max slavery level	Max slavery level
$Slavery exposure cooldown multiplier	Slavery exposure cooldown multiplier

$Disposition threshold	Disposition threshold
$Min days to join	Min days to join

$Update Status: {}	Update Status: {}
$Chance of dreamworld visits	Chance of dreamworld visits
$Immersive starts	Immersive starts
$SAFE WORD	SAFE WORD

$ Faction{} : {}	 Faction{} : {}
$     Days Since Joined: 	     Days Since Joined: 



$SD_KEYMAP_P2_SURRENDER_desc	The surrender key gives you the option to surrender willingly to your opponent or pray to Sanguine for help. In all cases, pressing this key will apply some safety checks and get you unstuck if you cannot move.
$_SDOID_config_T3_desc	Force gender of Sanguine in Dreamworld (or leave it to chance based on gender preferences)
$_SDOID_config_B14_desc	Uncheck if you want to delay visits to Dreamworld indefinitely. You will have to sleep in front of Sanguine's shrine to start the Dreamworld aspect of the mod manually. Look in the Help tab for a list of auto-start conditions.
$_SDOID_config_B21_desc	Emergency release from your current master - useful in case of friendly fire or static NPC.
$_SDOID_config_B10_desc	Toggle this ON to kneel before your Master while wearing an armbinder. 
$_SDOID_config_B11_desc	Toggle this ON to enable enslavement attempts from beasts (wolf, trolls, draugr, etc). 
$_SDOID_config_B12_desc	Toggle this ON to enable cage scenes at night (if a cage is nearby). 
$_SDOID_config_B13_desc	Toggle this ON to allow increasing random attacks based on number of visits to Sanguine's Dreamworld 
$_SDOID_config_S8_desc	Minimum value for slavery level (0 = defiant, 6 = total submissive). Should be lower than Max Slavery Level.
$_SDOID_config_S9_desc	Maximum value for slavery level (0 = defiant, 6 = total submissive). Should be higher than Min Slavery Level.
$_SDOID_config_S10_desc	Value multiplier to reduce (or increase) slavery exposure after each day of freedom. 0 removes slavery exposure after one night , 1.0 maintains slavery exposure at the same level, 2.0 increases slavery exposure over time (similar to withdrawal)
$_SDOID_config_S11_desc	Overall disposition to be considered for slave to be released (or disposed of). Use this as an Enslavement Difficulty setting.
$_SDOID_config_S1_desc	Adds a chance of success to the Death Alternative quests defined for Spriggan infection by SD.
$_SDOID_config_S2_desc	Adds a chance of success to the Death Alternative quests defined for enslavement by SD.
$_SDOID_config_S7_desc	Normal chance of visits to Sanguine's Dreamworld on sleep (after initial trigger conditions are met).
$This key is already mapped to '%s' (%s). Are you sure you want to continue?	This key is already mapped to '%s' (%s). Are you sure you want to continue?
$This key is already mapped to '%s'. Are you sure you want to continue?	This key is already mapped to '%s'. Are you sure you want to continue?
$_SDOID_config_S12_desc	Percent of Health to trigger chance of enslavement. Set to 0 if you are using Death Alternative or another mod sending mod events to SD+ for enslavement. 



$[SD] Cage scene - package end	[SD] Cage scene - package end
$[SD] Cage scene - package start	[SD] Cage scene - package start
$[SD]  - Cage is locked. Unlocking it.	[SD]  - Cage is locked. Unlocking it.
$[SD]  - Updating cage state.	[SD]  - Updating cage state.
$You submit to your aggressor...	You submit to your aggressor...
$You resist, but are forced to submit...	You resist, but are forced to submit...
$You manage to break free from your attacker...	You manage to break free from your attacker...
$You choose to insert the eggs inside you.	You choose to insert the eggs inside you.
$You choose to insert the worm inside you.	You choose to insert the worm inside you.
$You choose to put the plugs in.	You choose to put the plugs in.
$A heatwave of pleasure blossoms deep inside you.	A heatwave of pleasure blossoms deep inside you.
$A swarm of needles suddenly crawl under your skin.	A swarm of needles suddenly crawl under your skin.
$Host: Effect start	Host: Effect start
$Host: Effect end	Host: Effect end
$Your former master is looking for you	Your former master is looking for you
$You are free	You are free
$You arrive to your new home.	You arrive to your new home.
$[dream] Sanguine is welcoming you	[dream] Sanguine is welcoming you
$[dream] Sanguine is watching	[dream] Sanguine is watching
$[SNP] Starting scene...	[SNP] Starting scene...	
$The last traces of the roots are cleared from your body.	The last traces of the roots are cleared from your body.
$You think you could get away with that?!	You think you could get away with that?!
$You submit to a new owner.	You submit to a new owner.		
$Your new owner defeated you.	Your new owner defeated you.
$Your new owner strips you naked.	Your new owner strips you naked.
$Your owner inspects you carefully.	Your owner inspects you carefully.
$You are chained and collared.	You are chained and collared.
$You are marked as your owner's property.	You are marked as your owner's property.
$[SD] Slave Punishment	[SD] Slave Punishment
$Your owner is too far to punish you.	Your owner is too far to punish you.
$[SD] Slave Reward	[SD] Slave Reward
$Your owner is too far to remove your punishment.	Your owner is too far to remove your punishment.
$Not found!	Not found!
$[SD] Crawl override initialized	[SD] Crawl override initialized
$[SD] SD+ FNIS aa loaded	[SD] SD+ FNIS aa loaded
$The collar releases its grasp around your will...	The collar releases its grasp around your will...
$Your collar weighs around your neck...	Your collar weighs around your neck...
$[SD] SD cuffs detected	[SD] SD cuffs detected
$[SD] Yoke detected	[SD] Yoke detected
$[SD] Reset stance for Armbinder	[SD] Reset stance for Armbinder
$[SD] Reset stance for Yoke	[SD] Reset stance for Yoke
$[SD] Reset stance for Armbinder Elbow	[SD] Reset stance for Armbinder Elbow
$[SD] Reset stance for YokeBB	[SD] Reset stance for YokeBB
$[SD] Reset stance for Cuffs Front	[SD] Reset stance for Cuffs Front
$[SD] Reset stance for default standing	[SD] Reset stance for default standing
$[SD] Standing hands free override ON	[SD] Standing hands free override ON
$[SD] Slaver is Player!	[SD] Slaver is Player!
$Go away.. I already have enough slaves.	Go away.. I already have enough slaves.
$Go away.. Your master must be looking for you.	Go away.. Your master must be looking for you.
$Good slave... keep it coming.	Good slave... keep it coming.
$That's right.	That's right.
$What is this junk!?.	What is this junk!?.
$Good slave.	Good slave.
$Your owner is disinterested.	Your owner is disinterested.
$Your owner seems pleased.	Your owner seems pleased.
$Mmm.. that should hit the spot.	Mmm.. that should hit the spot.
$Well? What are you waiting for?.	Well? What are you waiting for?.
$Get back to work slave!	Get back to work slave!
$Your master groans happily.	Your master groans happily.
$(seems pleased)	(seems pleased)
$(shrugs)	(shrugs)
$The device remains locked in place (Non generic)	The device remains locked in place (Non generic)
$[SD] removing zad_BlockGeneric device!	[SD] removing zad_BlockGeneric device!
$[SD] equipDevice - bad keyword 	[SD] equipDevice - bad keyword 
$[SD] SD+ IS INSTALLING. 	[SD] SD+ IS INSTALLING. 
$MAKE SURE TO SAVE AND RELOAD ONCE ALL MESSAGES HAVE STOPPED.	MAKE SURE TO SAVE AND RELOAD ONCE ALL MESSAGES HAVE STOPPED.
$[SD] Error - empty task keyword - check logs for details	[SD] Error - empty task keyword - check logs for details
$[SD] Error - task name is empty - check logs for details	[SD] Error - task name is empty - check logs for details
$Your owner is too far to reward you.	Your owner is too far to reward you.
$(nevermind...)	(nevermind...)
$You don't need that much money either.	You don't need that much money either.
$[Resists weakly]	[Resists weakly]
$Dance for us...	Dance for us...
$Show us what you can do...	Show us what you can do...
$Help yourselves boys!...	Help yourselves boys!...
$Your mouth is held open as you are forced to swallow...	Your mouth is held open as you are forced to swallow...
$..some Skooma!	..some Skooma!
$In a stupor you start dancing for no reason...	In a stupor you start dancing for no reason...
$..some Ale!	..some Ale!
$Tendrils are digging deeper under your skin...	Tendrils are digging deeper under your skin...
$Sap is slowly pumping into your veins..	Sap is slowly pumping into your veins..
$Sweet sap runs down your legs...	Sweet sap runs down your legs...
$[SD] Issue with Spriggan root validation.	[SD] Issue with Spriggan root validation.
$The roots throb deeply in and out of you...	The roots throb deeply in and out of you...
$They force you to give them a good show.	They force you to give them a good show.
$They are not finished with you yet.	They are not finished with you yet.
$They surround you with lust in their eyes.	They surround you with lust in their eyes.
$You feel helpless as they take turns on you.	You feel helpless as they take turns on you.
$Another one is waiting for you.	Another one is waiting for you.
$You can't hide from the next aggressor.	You can't hide from the next aggressor.
$You feel weak as another one grabs you.	You feel weak as another one grabs you.
$Your follower has been enslaved!	Your follower has been enslaved!
$A new owner grabs you.	A new owner grabs you.
$You will regret attacking me!	You will regret attacking me!
$Your owner is either dead or left you...	Your owner is either dead or left you...
$Your owner is missing...	Your owner is missing...
$Your captors are watching...	Your captors are watching...
$Who said you could fight, Slave!	Who said you could fight, Slave!
$You better unequip that spell before I make you swallow it, Slave!	You better unequip that spell before I make you swallow it, Slave!
$Hold that torch higher, Slave!	Hold that torch higher, Slave!
$Better unequip that before I shove it up your ass, Slave!	Better unequip that before I shove it up your ass, Slave!
$You will regret this!	You will regret this!
$Your owner barks at you.	Your owner barks at you.
$Your owner wouldn't like that!	Your owner wouldn't like that!
$Your owner is looking for you!	Your owner is looking for you!
$There you are Slave... get your punishment, over here!	There you are Slave... get your punishment, over here!
$Your hands remain free.. lucky you.	Your hands remain free.. lucky you.
$Your previous owner fights back.	Your previous owner fights back.
$Your former owner leaves, disgusted.	Your former owner leaves, disgusted.
$Your owner binds your hands.	Your owner binds your hands.
$Your owner starts following you around.	Your owner starts following you around.
$You cling to your last breath...	You cling to your last breath...
$Your prayer goes unanswered...	Your prayer goes unanswered...
$You still have life in you...	You still have life in you...
$Kneeling...	Kneeling...
$You are not allowed to kneel	You are not allowed to kneel
$Standing...	Standing...
$You are not allowed to stand	You are not allowed to stand
$Already standing...	Already standing...
$Already crawling...	Already crawling...
$Crawling...	Crawling...
$[SD] Entering surrender state	[SD] Entering surrender state
$[SD] Surrender to combat target	[SD] Surrender to combat target
$[SD] Surrender to crosshair target	[SD] Surrender to crosshair target
$[SD] Aborting surrender	[SD] Aborting surrender
$[SD] Surrender to aggressor	[SD] Surrender to aggressor
$Your owner releases your hands.	Your owner releases your hands.
$You are not allowed to hold a weapon.  Your collar compels you to remove it.	You are not allowed to hold a weapon.  Your collar compels you to remove it.
$Your owner is in combat. Stay close...	Your owner is in combat. Stay close...
$You are too far from your owner...	You are too far from your owner...
$Your collar vibrates as you wander off.	Your collar vibrates as you wander off.
$Your collar stops vibrating.	Your collar stops vibrating.
$The collar is sending shocks.	The collar is sending shocks.
$Where did you think you were going?	Where did you think you were going?
$Your collar tightens as you wander off from the cage.	Your collar tightens as you wander off from the cage.
$The collar is choking you..	The collar is choking you..
$You are too far from the cage.	You are too far from the cage.
$Your collar tightens around your throat...	Your collar tightens around your throat...
$You are still far from the cage.	You are still far from the cage.
$Your breathing is painful...	Your breathing is painful...
$Your master is disappointed to find you without a collar.	Your master is disappointed to find you without a collar.
$Your master is too far to collar you again.	Your master is too far to collar you again.
$The shocks are making you hornier.	The shocks are making you hornier.
$Go to your cage.. right now!	Go to your cage.. right now!
$Now stay quiet for the rest of the night.	Now stay quiet for the rest of the night.
$The worst is over... for now..	The worst is over... for now..
$You are left to ponder your fate...	You are left to ponder your fate...
$You brace for the coming punishment...	You brace for the coming punishment...
$The whip leaves your skin on fire.	The whip leaves your skin on fire.
$You wince as the sight of the whip.	You wince as the sight of the whip.
$You slowly start to dance...	You slowly start to dance...
$SexLab cleanup: removing player from animating faction	SexLab cleanup: removing player from animating faction
$Go on...	Go on...
$Stop bugging me, Slave!	Stop bugging me, Slave!
$The creature suddenly humps you	The creature suddenly humps you
$You are mine now...	You are mine now...
$I don't like the way you look...	I don't like the way you look...
$Did you think I would fall for that?!	Did you think I would fall for that?!
$I want you to dance for me, Slave!	I want you to dance for me, Slave!
$Your captor's smile sends shivers down your spine	Your captor's smile sends shivers down your spine
$Your captor starts singing and cheering you on	Your captor starts singing and cheering you on
$[SNP] Your owner found you...	[SNP] Your owner found you...
$[SNP] Your owner is looking for you...	[SNP] Your owner is looking for you...
$Cleaning up devices	Cleaning up devices
$Done cleaning up devices	Done cleaning up devices
$You have no use for gold, slave..	You have no use for gold, slave..
$Get over here and get what's comming to you!	Get over here and get what's comming to you!
$Dance for me, Slave!	Dance for me, Slave!
$..some Spiced Wine!	..some Spiced Wine!
$..some Ale!	..some Ale
$Here comes your lesson, Slave!	Here comes your lesson, Slave!
$You shall dance for me, Slave!	You shall dance for me, Slave!
$You are forced to swallow...	You are forced to swallow...
$some Skooma!	some Skooma!
$Here it comes, Slave!	Here it comes, Slave!
$You will dance for me, Slave!	You will dance for me, Slave!
$Let's get some of this inside you...	Let's get some of this inside you...
$Umph... Skooma!	Umph... Skooma!
$Uhg... Wine!	Uhg... Wine!
$Ale?	Ale?
$You start dancing for some reason...	You start dancing for some reason...
$It's on now!	It's on now!
$That was idiotic,...Slave!	That was idiotic,...Slave!
$...some dick!	...some dick!
$Your captor is forcing you to dance...	Your captor is forcing you to dance...
$The sweet scent of your sap drenched skin is irresistible...	The sweet scent of your sap drenched skin is irresistible...
$The roots force your legs open ...	The roots force your legs open ...
$The sweet scent is overwhelming...	The sweet scent is overwhelming...
$Get on your knees and lift up that ass of yours...	Get on your knees and lift up that ass of yours...